我觉得没那个必要吧
I'm not sure that was necessary.
我也觉得是
Neither am I.
不是罗拉因为发现哈维尔跟塔莎鬼混而起了杀心
It wasn't Lola who caught Javier and Tasha fooling around.
是塔莎的男朋友妒火中烧
It was Tasha's jealous boyfriend.
妒火中烧的男朋友  哈
A jealous boyfriend, huh?
虽然阿蒂竭力想要撇清
Artie may have been trying
他自己的关系
to deflect attention away from himself,
但这条线索确实值得跟
but it's a lead worth following up.
就是他 塔莎的前男友
There he is. Tasha's ex.
有着耀眼的水晶般双眸
The one with the gleaming crystal eyes
嘴唇就像刚吃完桃子意犹未尽
and the mouth that looks like it just finished eating a peach.
你直接告诉我他穿着什么颜色的衣服就成了
How about you just tell me what color shirt he's wearing?
蔚蓝色
Cerulean.
周二6点到7点那段时间
What were you doing on Tuesday
你在做什么
between the hours of 6:00 and 7:00?
我在家  一个人
I was at home. Alone.
怎么可能呢
How did that happen?
里维拉先生  你有多高
How tall are you, Mr. Rivera?
6尺3英寸（大约190cm）
I'm 6'3.
你第一次听到
When did you first learn about...
我能问个问题吗
Can I just ask a question?
你是否有着印第安血统
Do you have a little Native American in your ancestry
因为你的颧骨
'cause those cheekbones...
摩尔小姐
Miss Moore!
哦 对不起
Oh. Sorry.
我有四分之一彻罗基族血统
I'm a quarter Cherokee.
你看 我就说是嘛
Yeah, you are.
我是不是有必要让你出去啊
Do I need to ask you to leave?
你是什么时候知道你女朋友跟哈维尔在一起的
When did you first learn about your girlfriend and Javier?
是前女友
Ex-girlfriend.
我不记得了
And I don't remember.
你不记得什么时候发现你女朋友出轨了
You don't remember discovering your girlfriend cheating on you?
我不想钻牛角尖
I don't like to dwell on things.
再说了 她也得到报应了
Besides, she got what was coming to her.
哈维尔几个月前为了一个更年轻的小妞把她给甩了
Javier dumped her a few months ago for a younger version.
她就是为了那样的人离开我的
That's the kind of guy she left me for.
他睡了自己最好朋友的18岁的女儿
Someone who'll bang his best friend's 18-year-old daughter.
阿蒂
Artie?
他经纪人的女儿
His manager's daughter?
对 贝卡
Yeah. Becca.
在贵圈是保不住这样的秘密的
It's a not-too-well-kept secret around the art community.
但你可别说是从我这儿听到的
But you didn't hear it from me.
我得请你喝一杯
You gotta let me buy you a drink.
我今天得活的有意义一些
I need something in the win column today.
我觉得你得把标准定得高一点
I think you need to set the bar a little bit higher.
请人喝杯酒
Buying somebody a drink
可不算是什么成就
doesn't seem like much of an accomplishment.
那得看我之前你拒绝了多少人了
That depends on how many guys you turned down before I got here.
所以
So...
你怎么会一个人
What brings you here to drink alone
在这样美好的夜晚喝着闷酒
and stare off into the top-shelf liquor on this fine evening?
可以理解成 生活无处不惊喜啊
Let's just say life takes some surprising turns.
可不是吗
Doesn't it, though?
如果一年前有人告诉我
If someone were to tell me a year ago
我今天的生活会是什么样子
that my life would be like it is today,
我肯定一记响拳就上去了
I would've punched him in the face.
听着
Listen,
你挺有魅力
you're incredibly charming,
但是我不怎么喜欢姐弟恋
but the age difference isn't something I'm into.
哎呀  那真是可惜了
Well, that is a shame.
虽然我寂寞得很
Because I am lonely as hell and the idea of trying
但是想到让我跟一个25岁的酒吧女郎搭讪的话
to have a conversation with some 25-year-old
还不如
as she swipes through Tinder,
让我一头撞死在吧台上
makes me want to impale myself on that bar tap.
还好我们还能愉快的聊天
Well, there's no reason why we can't have a nice chat.
当然了
Sure there is.
进来吧
Come on in.
嘿 不管谁在这个叫丽芙的女人身体里面
Hey, pod person who's taken over Liv's body,
你好歹做点家务吧
you really should've done some homework
因为没人会买你的画的
because no one is going to buy this.
对不起  我刚才有点入神了
Sorry. I was kind of in the zone or something.
嗨
Hi.
如果你在家造火箭
I would literally be less surprised to come in here
恐怕我都没觉得有这个稀奇
and find you building a rocket ship.
这是新爱好
It's a new hobby.
不敢相信这可是一个认为爱好是仅限
This coming from the girl who said
12岁以下 65岁以上人士的女人说的
hobbies were for people under 12 or over 65.
我什么时候说那样的话了
When did I say that?
都说了好几年了
Repeatedly. Over the course of several years.
但我一直认为你那么说只是为了
But I think you were just trying to talk me out of
让我别捣鼓我做户外家具的事
making my own outdoor furniture,
但至今我还是觉得那是个好点子
which I still think I'd be kind of awesome at.
等等  你这听的是查特・贝克吗
And, I'm sorry, are you listening to Chet Baker?
原来他叫这名字啊  我喜欢他的歌
Is that who this is? I am loving him.
你怎么着
You're what?
我试着让你接受爵士乐都好几年了
I tried to get you to listen to jazz for years.
我曾经花费几个礼拜时间给你做混音CD
I spent weeks strategically arranging the perfect mix CD for you
然后你听两首就受不了了
and you stopped listening after two songs.
这张CD好像就是你给我的
I think this is the CD.
你说你觉得无结构的音乐是孤芳自赏
You said you thought the lack of structure was narcissistic
你宁愿挺锅碗瓢盆都不愿听这个
and you'd rather listen to someone dropping cutlery.
我过去怎么那么混蛋
Why was I such a jerk?
谁知道
Who knows?
我忍你的事情可不止这一件
It was just one of the many things I accepted
谁叫你那么火辣呢
because you're super-hot.
开玩笑的
I'm kidding,
有点开玩笑啦
to a degree.
如果你真的喜欢这张CD的话
If you're really liking this CD,
我还有一堆好听的可以给你再录
I have a bunch of stuff on vinyl I could record for you.